    analytics: {
      autoScan: true,
      title: {
        en: "Analytics & Reports",
        ar: "التحليلات والتقارير"
      },
      description: {
        en: "Master your university's data insights and reporting capabilities",
        ar: "أتقن رؤى البيانات وقدرات التقارير في جامعتك"
      },
      steps: [
        {
          id: 1,
          target: ".flex.flex-col.md\\:flex-row.justify-between",
          title: {
            en: "Analytics Command Center",
            ar: "مركز قيادة التحليلات"
          },
          content: {
            en: "Welcome to your comprehensive analytics hub! This is where you access all university data insights. Use the filters to customize reports by department and time period.",
            ar: "مرحبا بك في مركز التحليلات الشامل! هنا تحصل على جميع رؤى بيانات الجامعة. استخدم المرشحات لتخصيص التقارير حسب القسم والفترة الزمنية."
          },
          position: "bottom"
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          target: ".flex.flex-wrap.gap-2",
          title: {
            en: "Navigation Tabs",
            ar: "علامات التنقل"
          },
          content: {
            en: "Switch between different analytics categories here. Each tab provides specialized insights: Admissions, Financial, Academic, Student Engagement, Placement, and Compliance data.",
            ar: "تبديل بين فئات التحليلات المختلفة هنا. كل علامة تبويب توفر رؤى متخصصة: القبول المالية الأكاديمية مشاركة الطلاب التوظيف وبيانات الامتثال."
          },
          position: "bottom"
        }
      ]
    },
